

D. Conner Borkowski

SUMMARY

Community advocate & student passionate about extending experience to build the capacity of groups & individuals. Especially dedicated to raising voices of historically marginalized groups, promoting justice, equity, diversity, & inclusion (JEDI) initiatives, & utilizing outdoor recreation as a tool for equity.

DESIGN SKILLS

Stakeholder & Community Engagement

Intermediate ArcGIS Online

Advanced Written & Verbal Communication Skills

Facilitation & Education

Project Management

Data Management & Analysis

Photography, Videography, & Design

EDUCATION

University of Colorado Boulder - Masters for the Environment

August 2022 - May 2024

Focus in Sustainability in the Outdoor Industry

Masters for the Environment Merit Scholarship

North Carolina State University - B.S. Computer + B.S Electrical

Engineering

August 2018 - May 2022

Minors in Art+Design & Outdoor Leadership

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Masters for the Environment - Media Graduate Student Assistant

September 2022 - Present

Key Accomplishments:

• Updated media database to not include external stock images.

Responsibilities:

- Responsible for building the media base that accurately represents the community.
- Manage videography & recording of guest speaker events.
- Assist in engaging prospective students at open houses & other visits.

Outdoor Adventures at NC State - Instructor + Trip Leader

February 2019 - May 2022

Key Accomplishments:

- Achieved Trip Leader of the Year in 2022
- Managed relationships & set expectations to open a state-of-the-art climbing center.
- Collaborated with affinity groups to hold climbing related events.

Responsibilities:

- Carried out complex trip plans.
- Worked in cross-functional teams to support educational missions.
- Programmed year-long plans for all trip leads.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Embedded Machine Learning Club at NC State - Founder & COO

July 2021 - May 2022

Key Accomplishments:

- Developed a JEDI statement for the club.
- Launched the club from 5 founding members to 25 active members.
- Raised more than \$10,000 in club funds in the first year.

Responsibilities:

- Established branding & curriculum for the club's image.
- Envisioned & pursued the mission of education, practical application, & community collaboration.

Engineers Without Borders at NC State - VP of Projects & Team Lead

December 2018 - January 2021

Key Accomplishments:

- Completed & closed 3 international projects.
- Followed rigorous guidelines for community engagement & involvement throughout project work.

Responsibilities:

- Maintained social, financial, & environmental sustainability of all 4 engineering projects.
- Engaged stakeholders about project health & progress.

Habitat for Humanity Wake County - Volunteer Consultant

August 2019 - December 2019

Key Accomplishments:

- Completed 3 interactive GIS maps relating property values, public transportation, & Habitat for Humanity housing projects.
- Presented findings & recommendations to Habitat for Humanity Wake County Board of Directors.

HONORS & CERTIFICATIONS

North Carolina State University Caldwell Fellow - Class of 2022 Certified NC State Campus Conversations Project Facilitator - 2021 Wilderness First Responder - December 2021